Boyka is back!
Boyka: Undisputed IV is a action, drama, thriller
film directed by Todor Chapkanov.
In the fourth installment of the fighting franchise, Boyka is shooting for the big leagues when
an accidental death in the ring makes him question everything he stands for.
When he finds out the wife of the man he accidentally killed is in trouble, Boyka offers to
fight in a series of impossible battles to free her from a life of servitude.
Yuri Boyka, played by Scott Adkins.
Alma, played by Teodora Duhovnikova.
Zourab, played by Alon Aboutboul.
Slava, played by Julian Vergov.
Koshmar, played by Martyn Ford.
Igor Kazmir, played by Brahim Achabbakhe.
Boyka: Undisputed (also known as Boyka: Undisputed 4), is a 2016 martial arts action film directed by
Todor Chapkanov, and written by David White and Tony Mosher from a story by Boaz Davidson.
It is the sequel to Undisputed III: Redemption (2010), and the
fourth installment overall in the Undisputed franchise.
Scott Adkins reprises his role as Yuri Boyka.
The film explores themes of prison, sports, wife, affectation, sequel.
The tone is emotional and intense.